Advanced Dentistry by Soboh Liswi Tedini

* [Pomona Location  
    101 West Mission Blvd., #221, Pomona, CA 91766](https://www.sobohliswidental.com/contact_us_info/)
* [Newport Beach NEW Location  
    20072 SW Birch Street, Newport Beach, CA 92660](https://www.sobohdentalcare.com/)
*   
    Menu

* Menu

* [Our Services](javascript:void(0);)
    
    Soboh, Liswi, & Tedini
    
    Our Services

    * * *
    
* [Patient Info](javascript:void(0);)
    
    Patient Section
    
    For Patients

* [About Us](javascript:void(0);)
    
    About Us
    
    Office Info

Privacy Policy

\> Privacy Policy

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

We collect anonymous demographic data:

* Overview (overview of traffic by age and gender)
* Age (traffic by age ranges)
* Gender (traffic by gender)
* Interests
* Overview (overview of traffic by affinity and other categories)
* Affinity Categories (behavior by affinity categories)
* In-Market Categories (behavior by in-market categories)
* Other Categories (behavior by other interest categories)

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

If you would like to opt-out Google developed the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. [Google opt out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience

(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

To improve our website

(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

To improve customer service

(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, our website may not function properly. However, you can still receive information over the telephone by contacting our office.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

LEGAL DISCLAIMER

For the purpose of illustrating the possibilities of today's dental procedures, this web site may include models and/or generic before and after smile case examples. These examples do not represent a certainty of case performance for any single individual. Individual before and after results will vary. Patients should consult with their dentist before making a final decision. All patient information is private and protected by our office unless otherwise approved by the patient.

**CONNECT** with us

×Close
